<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on masoudkf</title><link>http://example.org/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on masoudkf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Git 101</title><link>http://example.org/posts/git-101/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/git-101/</guid><description>
Git basics. This post is part of the course material for ENSF 381 (W23) at the University of Calgary.</description></item><item><title>Gatsby on AWS: Creating a CI/CD Pipeline</title><link>http://example.org/posts/aws-cicd-pipeline-for-gatsby/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/aws-cicd-pipeline-for-gatsby/</guid><description>
Gatsby is a super-fast static website generator that&amp;rsquo;s been getting a lot of attention lately. For one, this very website was (proudly) made with Gatsby. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with it, I encourage you to definitely check it out; spoiler alert: it&amp;rsquo;s awesome. For one, it uses React which we love! (By the way, React website itself was made with Gatsby)
This post is not about how to build Gatsby websites; rather, it&amp;rsquo;s on how you can create a CI/CD pipeline and deploy your Gatsby website on AWS.</description></item><item><title>A Simple Parent Class for JADE Agents</title><link>http://example.org/posts/jade-super-agent/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/jade-super-agent/</guid><description>
In this article, I will not talk about how JADE works. I assume that you are already familiar with the framework. If this is not the case, you can check out JADE website first. Let&amp;rsquo;s get to it.
Communication is the heart of every agent-based system. If your agents do not talk to one another, what&amp;rsquo;s the point of having them? In order to establish connections between your agents (a.k.a sending messages), you need to have the destination address.</description></item></channel></rss>